vitalitygames.com 2019-01-29

# Privacy Policy - VitalityGames.com

Welcome!

This Privacy Policy governs the VitalityGames.com website and it applies to all of Vitality Games services and products. You should be aware that Vitality Games cannot be held responsible for the privacy policy of other sites and sources. By accessing VitalityGames.com, you are consenting to this Privacy Policy.

Whenever important changes are made to this policy, we will ask for your consent once again. Vitality Games respects the privacy of all users of its site and shall ensure the personal information you provide is treated confidentially.

We are aware of the trust you place in us. We see it as our responsibility to protect your privacy. On this page, we will let you know what information we collect when you use our site, why we collect it and how we improve your user experience. Thus, you will understand exactly how we work.

### A. Which data do we collect?

Our visitors privacy is important to us and we recognize the need to provide additional privacy protection where is needed. Younger visitors should always check with their parents or guardians before entering information on any website and we encourage families to discuss their household guidelines regarding the online sharing of personal information.

#### 1\. Data we received from you

Only when you fill in the contact form provided on our website or subscribe for new games, we will process only two types of personal data: name and email.

#### 2\. Data we receive automatically

On your visit to our website there is certain information that we collect from traffic references of hosting server. We can collect some personal data through the use of cookies: see [Cookie Consent](https://www.vitalitygames.com/cookie-consent.html "Cookie Consent"). Some other (personal) data can be collected without the use of cookies. They can only be read and used during your visit to our site: IP-address (used e.g. for preventing double voting),browser type and revision, (mobile) device type.

Related to traffic references of hosting servers. Every time you check out a website, there is certain information you make available for collection such as internet domain, IP address, time of visit, location, type of browser and operating system used to access our site, pages you visit, the address of that website and so on. Like others, we collect this information and use it for visitors statistics and to improve our services to you.

#### 3\. Data we receive from third parties

When we receive Personal Information from third parties we will inform you personally.

### B. Why do we collect these data? Based on which legal ground?

Your personal data will be used to enable us to optimise the services we render and the content we provide. In certain cases when we are under a legal requirement to process personal data, like age limits, we will process these personal data. Secondly, we may use your personal data for direct marketing purposes, such as updates on new or existing games and newsletters. You will only receive electronic direct marketing communications from third parties if you have given us your explicit consent by ticking the box provided on our site.

We may also use your personal data for statistical purposes and to improve our services and product (see Privacy Policy for [Android/iOS apps](https://www.vitalitygames.com/privacy-policy-apps.html "Privacy Policy for apps")). These processing activities are thus based on a justified legitimate interest of Vitality Games.

### C. Data retention periods

Your personal data will only be processed for as long as this is necessary for the purposes mentioned above. Unless there is a justified reason to retain the personal data, for example within the framework of customer relation management, your personal data will be deleted one month after you failed to visit our site during a consecutive period of two years.

### D. Your rights

You can get access to your personal data and rectify or erase them, free of charge. You also have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. If you do not wish to receive newsletters or information about our products or services, you can at any moment and without any need for justification, object to the processing of your personal data for these purposes ("unsubscribe"). You can do this by sending us an e-mail. You can also do this by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our advertising e-mails. Moreover, you have the right to data portability for the personal data you have provided to Vitality Games.

To exercise these rights, we ask you to send a clear request, to the email address mentioned below, that states clearly what it is you want to know, rectify or erase. This request needs to be signed and dated and contain a copy of the front side of your identity card. You should specifically motivate your request if you want to rectify or erase personal data or restrict the processing thereof. Once these conditions are fulfilled, Vitality Games will execute your request as soon as possible and send you a message on this matter.

### E. Security measures

Vitality Games has taken all reasonable and appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure that your Personal Information is processed securely. If you have any questions on these security measures, feel free to contact us at the email address mentioned below. Within Vitality Games, the personal data are only available for people who need to have access to them in relation to their job. At no moment in time we will sell or rent out your personal data to Third parties. Occasionally we may use an external processor. If we do this, we will always ensure that your information is handled confidentially and in a safe manner. We also always draw up a contract with these processors. This way the processor will never be allowed to use your data on their own initiative and your data has to be erased as soon as the processor has finished the assignment.

### F. Contact information of data controller

For all your questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact us at the following e-mail address: data-protection@vitalitygames.com or through our contact form.
